discoveryarticles.com 2010-01-31

# Privacy | DiscoveryArticles.com

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

�To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

�To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

�To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used� to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements and.

We also use Google advertising to monetize DiscoveryArticles.com.� By using Google advertising on DiscoveryArticles.com we must alert you with the following:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on DiscoveryArticles.com site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only  
  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms and Condition

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.discoveryarticles.com/pages/Guidelines.html>.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.discoveryarticles.com  
administrator@discoveryarticles.com
